searchyellowdirectory.com 2019-06-02

# Privacy - SearchYellowDirectory.com

Welcome to our website, Searchyellowdirectory.com.

See below our New 2018 Updated EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) under; **Cookies and Google Adsense** SYD uses cookies from Google to deliver its services, to personalize ads and to analyze traffic. Information about your use of this site is shared with Google. By using SearchYellowDirectory.com, you agree to its use of cookies. **Please see below in section Cookies and Google Adsense.**  

Use of this website, and any information distributed throughout, is offered to you on your acceptance of our Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions, our Terms of Use and other notices posted on this website. Your use of this website or of any content presented in any and all areas of the website indicates your acknowledgment and agreement to these Terms and Conditions, our Privacy Policy and other notices posted on this website. If you do not agree to be bound by and comply with all of the foregoing, you are not permitted to use any of the search tools or any of the content contained within this website, This privacy policy sets out how SearchYellowDirectory.com uses and protects any information that you give SearchYellowDirectory.com when you use this website. SearchYellowDirectory.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (e-mail address) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. If we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. SearchYellowDirectory.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective May 1, 2007. Please note this policy applies only to information collected by Search Yellow Directory and does not impact information collected or used by SearchYellowDirectory.com affiliates through other means.

Privacy Statement:

SearchYellowDirectory.com does expect that its partners, advertisers and third-party affiliates do respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other search content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. Please be aware that SearchYellowDirectory.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements and policies of all third parties when being linked to other websites.

What we collect:

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
  * Like most websites, SearchYellowDirectory.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools (cookies) that may be transparent to our visitors.

Note: Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You may set your browser to refuse to accept cookies but doing so may limit your ability to access certain portions of the site or may require you to re-enter your user name and password. Additionally we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences.

Cookies and Google Adsense

SearchYellowDirectory does not collect or store cookies. However we do use information collected by the user browser to hold on to information, such as city and state location. This provides the user with better targeted landing pages. We do display Google Adsense which serves cookies to deliver its services, to personalize ads and to analyze traffic. Information about your use of this site is shared with Google. As of May 25, 2018 there is a new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We have updated our privacy policies in order to conform with the new regulations. By using this site, you agree to its use of cookies.

When does AdSense send cookies to a browser?

Google AdSense sends a cookie to the user's browser after any impression, click, or other activity that results in a call to Google servers. If the browser accepts the cookie, the cookie is stored on the browser. Most commonly, AdSense sends a cookie to the browser when a user visits a page that shows Google ads. Pages with Google ads include ad tags that instruct browsers to request ad content from Google servers. When the server delivers the ad content, it also sends a cookie. But a page doesn’t have to show Google ads for this to happen; it just needs to include Adsense ad tags, which might load a click tracker or impression pixel instead. [How does AdSense use cookies?](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/7549925?hl=en)

What we do with the information we gather:

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We will use your information only as permitted by law.
  * Internal record keeping.
  * Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways.
  * We only use the data you input to provide you with a request and do not use it for any other purpose.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * We do not and will not share any of your Personally Identifiable Information, including your email addresses, collected by SearchYellowDirectory.com

Security:

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Children:

SearchYellowDirectory.com does not and will not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 years of age except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that SearchYellowDirectory.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us through our Feedback & Comments Page.

Website Disclaimer:

SearchYellowDirectory.com acts as a gateway to the information of publicly available-public records. The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. While we endeavour to keep the information up-to-date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event shall SearchYellowDirectory.com be liable for any ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER DAMAGES, including any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits out of, or in connection with the use of this website.

Publicly Available Records Disclaimer:

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of SearchYellowDirectory.com. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. SearchYellowDirectory.com does not maintain a database of personal records or yellow pages business listings, therefore it is not possible to change the information it finds from various public records sources. SearchYellowDirectory.com can not remove personal information or business listings it finds because SearchYellowDirectory.com has no legal control to add, modify or delete public information owned, operated and-or maintained by other sources. Other sites may operate under different user agreements than this Site. We encourage you to review applicable policies and agreements when you visit any website.

Every effort is made to keep our website up and running smoothly. However, SearchYellowDirectory.com takes no responsibility or will not be held liable for the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

How to Contact Us:

Please contact us through our Feedback page.

We may update this privacy policy from time to time, so please check back often.

July 2, 2018.
